I, Carol, will be heading out soon.
Wait for me, Noel.
Sora no
Method
negaigoto yureru oto sotto hisomeru
Snow falls gently past my face,
hoho no soba de mau yukitachi
and my fears and hopes are forgotten.
takusan no koukai kako wo musubu egaotachi
Your smile takes away all of my past regrets,
kitakaze no sasayaki kurete tokeru
and they melt into the arcadian north wind.
fuyuzora no samishisa wo kasanete
I'll embrace the emptiness I feel on this wintery night
yasashisa no hitomi koete
and look into your gentle eyes.
ima tsutaetai melody
This melody I'll share with you now
yubisashita ichibanboshi hikaru sora ni
is like the light of a single star shining in the sky,
kakiatsumeta mirai kajikanda yubi no sukima tooru seiza tachi
Keep holding onto your destiny so it won't slip through your numb fingers.
aa kono basho kara mita keshiki kanaetai
Oh, how I wish I could make this view come true.
yakusoku ne
I promise you one day I will.
One More Wish of Mine
There.
I'm off!
Aren't you going to eat?
I'll be eating out. Sorry!
Ah... take care.
I was pretty confident about this, too.
It's been pretty lively lately,
but it's just the two of us today, isn't it?
Ow!
W-What was that?
NOZOMI
TEA HOUSE AND EATERY
Welcome to our restaurant!
Nonoka!
Were you able to help much?
Yup!
Welcome, Nonoka!
Noel was a really big help.
She's good with the customers, too.
And I'm going to keep working hard!
Wipe, wipe! Wipe, wipe! Wipe, wipe!
Thank you for your patience.
Here's your house special omelette rice!
Thanks, Noel!
Noel.
Yes?
Want to eat it with me?
Yeah!
Hi there.
Are you lost?
No, I'm not.
That Souta, going abroad to study.
Without even helping out here, either.
Is he going abroad starting next month?
He'sh jusht doing prepharationsh.
He'll be bahck shoon.
Waitress, dear.
You've got a customer.
It's from Shione!
Shione's similing!
I want to see her again.
Yeah.
Hey, Shione's birthday is coming soon, isn't it?
What's everyone getting her?
A birthday! A birthday!
What's a birthday?
Oh, um...
It's the day you were born.
Everyone celebrates it with you.
What should we get her?
Shione's a sucker for sweets,
so maybe a year's supply of hot spring buns?
That's a bit imposing, don't you think?
Huh? Really?
The day you were born...
Noel.
Are you alright?
I'm always in a good mood!
It seemed like the whole
birthday thing bothered you.
I'm a disc,
so I don't really know when I was born.
But,
As long as everyone is happy,
even if it's not my birthday,
I'll smile cheerfully every day.
So will I.
I'm sure everyone else will, too.
All thanks to you, Noel.
Not again!
I'm home.
I'm home!
Welcome back, you two!
Thank you for the meal.
Hey Dad, can I ask a favour?
Oh?
What makes you want to see them all of a sudden?
The photos from seven years ago?
I want to do a bit of digging in the past.
Is that so?
Huh?
I think it's around here...
Ah, found it.
It's full of photos I have no memories of...
When we took those photos,
you didn't want to look.
I really didn't, did I?
Is this it?
First snow
I thought so.
That was the day.
What about the first snow of the season?
That was the day we called the disc.
What about it?
It's Noel's birthday!
Noel!
Huh?
Oh...
What are you saying?
What?
We discs appear when strong, pure wishes are made.
When one wish is granted,
we move on to grant another wish.
Um...
And yet, I have to ask,
just how long are you planning to stay in this town?
I want...
... to always...
... be in this town.
You can't do that!
There are lots and lots more wishes
that need to be granted.
You've granted their wishes already, haven't you?
Yeah...
Everyone is happy.
Then you don't have any reason to stay, right?
Let's go, Noel.
Wait.
Nonoka...
Don't get in our way, please.
Sorry about that.
Are you one of Noel's friends?
F-Fr...?!
She's my friend!
Y-You're wrong!
My name is Carol.
I'm a disc, like Noel.
A disc?
I came to bring her back.
But...
I want...
I want to be with Nonoka
and everyone else, too!
I don't get it.
The duty of a disc is to make lots
of wishes come true, you know!
Carol...
Carol!
I...
Don't tell me...
I was just rejected, wasn't I?
I want to be with Nonoka,
and everyone else, too.
What does that mean?
"Granting wishes is a disc's duty."
Huh?
Disc?
That's it!
If the disc leaves this town, Noel will leave as well!
I should make a wish on my disc!
Huh?
My disc...
Where's my disc?
Is...
Is this it?
Travelling here used up too much energy, didn't it?
Mr. Disc, Mr. Disc!
Mr. Disc, please grant my wish!
I wish to drive out Noel's disc!
I wish to bring Noel back home!
The effect might not be strong enough by myself.
Mr. Disc, Mr. Disc, please grant my wish!
I wish to drive out Noel's disc!
Please grant my wish, Mr. Disc, Mr. Disc!
Drive out Noel, drive out her disc!
Away from this town,
Mr. Disc, drive them out!
Noel's birthday?
Yeah. I figured the day
we called the disc is Noel's birthday.
Agreed!
If that's the case, why don't we
throw her a birthday party?
We can reserve my family's restaurant.
Don't we need permission?
It's fine, it's fine!
Noel is a precious family member, after all.
Ah, I almost forgot!
Let's invite Shione, too.
Shione,
Happy Birthday!!
Hot spring buns
1 year's supply!!
A year's supply?
Not even close.
Shione said she'd come!
That was quick!
By the way, should I send Souta an invitation, too?
Isn't he overseas?
He should be home around then, so it should be fine.
That's great. Having everyone come will make Noel so happy!
L-Let's drive out the disc away from this town!
That disc cannot stay in this town!
Huh? What was that?
Disc?
Your cooperation is,
um, greatly appreciated!
Let's talk...
Carol...
Man, I can't stand to watch this anymore!
You've got to project more!
Give me that!
Huh?
Let's drive the disc away from this town!
Just like that. Oppose the disc!
Well then. We should stop them, shouldn't we?
You've got to do it from your diaphragm.
Oppose the disc!
You don't say?
What?
What's your name?
C-Carol!
Carol! Hand those out!
Yes, ma'am!
Oppose the disc
Go home!!
Why am I caught up in this mess?
Even this is all her fault—
Here.
And whose fault do you think this is?
I'm sorry.
You've already granted their wishes,
and yet you're still spouting nonsense?
That's what I thought at first, too.
"With this, Nonoka and her
friends' wishes are granted."
But...
This is about the wishes Noel granted for us, right?
Noel's smile... if she isn't happy,
she can't grant wishes.
I don't get it at all.
Then, her disc...
What are you saying? I don't understand any of it!
Hey, get back here!
Dear customer...
Carol! Mr. Monster!
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry!
It's okay.
Good work, you two.
It's sweet!
This is bitter.
Just perfect.
Yummy!
Lake Kiriya
Hot Springs Hotel
Voucher
Lake Kiriya
Hot Springs Hotel
Voucher
Consolation Prize
Lake Kiriya Hot Springs Hotel
PLANETARIUM
I hope Carol will come, too.
You're
invited
Noel's             Birthday
Party
Reserved
today
Nozomi
Reserved
today
Nozomi
I'm back.
Should I let them know what time the bus is coming, just in case?
How's this?
Maybe just a bit more to the right.
Oh, come on!
Stupid Souta, when is he coming home?
It's like he's already bailed on us.
Souta
You're
invited
Noel's             Birthday
Party
It would have been nice for even one of them to wait for me.
Shione!
Long time no see, Yuzuki.
Koharu and Nonoka, too.
It's been a while.
Shione,
thanks for coming!
There was no question about it.
We're celebrating Noel's first birthday, after all.
Where's Noel?
She's probably with Carol.
Carol?
Oh, yes.
What are you up to?
It's hard for me to go in.
But it's your house.
I've been away for a while.
If you're saying that after being gone for only a short while,
what will you do when you're gone for years?
I have no idea.
I guess not.
Come on, let's go in!
There's lots of work to be done,
and we need your help!
Hey!
NOZOMI
TEA HOUSE AND EATERY
Let me off first!
I hope she likes it.
That girl...
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Really, it's nothing.
Please don't scooch over next to me!
But this here is my spot.
I've been sitting here for years.
It's a place where I get answers to the littlest things.
I bet,
right now, you're just like how I was back then.
I'm not really worried about anything.
It's just that, well,
I don't really know what to do.
I just know that my acquaintance is there.
Then it's simple, isn't it?
It is?
Do you like her? Do you not?
That girl, I mean.
You love her,
yet you aren't honest about your feelings.
You can't just wrestle with your feelings forever.
You'll only hurt her in the end.
You're scared of being betrayed.
However,
that's all in your head.
Um...
What are you trying to say?
I'm just speaking about myself.
Take your true feelings and try trusting them.
Wait!
I've decided!
I will... Noel...
Where...
Where is it?
Maybe Mr. Fox took it.
I'm sorry, No—
Carol.
Noel!
I came to invite you, Carol.
Let's go together!
Don't worry.
Today is my birthday...
Noel
Carol
...and yours, too!
I thought
that when you came to this town,
that just maybe...
Mr. Disc?
My disc...
My disc's power has returned!
What?
Noel?
It looks like I was called.
Called to the disc.
That can't... but...
Why are you—
No way...
No! You can't go!
It's all my fault.
It's all my fault!
Carol.
Cheer up.
Because...
... I understand...
... that you came to this town...
... to make my wish come true!
The wish that Noel made!
Mr. Disc, Mr. Disc, please grant my wish!
Please make Noel's wish come true!
I wish that Noel will be together with the ones she loves
forever and ever!
Thank you, Carol.
Noel?
No...
Why?
Mr. Disc?
I want...
... to be with Noel...
... to be with her beloved Noel...
... forever and ever!
Let's go together.
They're rather late...
Did you tell them what time to come?
We at least did that much.
Should we go look for them?
Let's wait a little longer.
What's wrong?
It's snowing.
Oh, it's just snow?
It's the first snow of the season!
Speaking of which, that day was
the first snow of the season, too, wasn't it?
No...
Was it?
Nonoka?
yureru minamo sono fukaku ni
The azure sky is as vast as the sea
aoi uchuu utsuttetane
forever reflected by the waves.
mirai... soshite mata chitteiku kisetsu oboeteiru?
Don't you realize our futures are changing with the seasons?
watashitachi wa unmei tsumugi nagara
We merely pave the paths leading to our fates,
sono ito ga doko made
unaware of how far those strings
tsuzuiteku no ka shiranai mama de
would continue to be entwined.
tada soko ni
But...
inspiration yorokobi toka kotoba wo wakachiau tabi
These words that we share bring me joy and life,
aa itsuka owari no hi ga kuru sou kanji saseru yo
but still I know these days must come to an end.
initialize sono tobira wo akeru toki ga kuru no darou
One day, I'll have to open the door to truly start my life.
kirei na toki wo tojikomete
I'll shut all those cheerful times behind me,
mizuumi ni shizumeta no
and bury them in a place I'll never reach again,
and bury them in a place I'll never reach again.
dakedo watashi heiki dayo to
but I tell myself that it'll all be okay
hoshi no tayori ni tsuzuru
if I have these stars here to guide me.
Noel
Carol